1994년, 기밀 지역
TOP SECRET LOCATION, 1994
항복합니다 스승님
I yield, sensei.
집중을 안하는군
또 말이야
You are unfocused, again.
- 항복합니다
- 너무 느려
- I yield.
- Too slow.
다시!
Again!
존, 지금 전혀
집중을 안하고 있어
Your center is filled
with conflict, John.
평정심을 찾지 않으면
절대 날 이길 수 없을거야
Until you find your calm center,
you will never beat me.
애교있는 웃음은
아무도 못 이겨요
You can't beat
a winning smile, John.
소매시장에선 더더욱이요
Not in retail sales.
손님들에게 그 하얀이를 보이세요
You need to show your customers those pearly whites.
뭐 하얗진 않지만요
미백 좀 하셔야겠네요
Well, soon-to-be pearly whites.
You need to bleach them.
당신도 사람이란걸 보여주세요
Just show them you
got a pulse, Casey.
"안녕하세요?" 인사도 좀 하시고
Give 'em a "Hey, how ya doin?"
"그건 거기 둬. 친구"
Or a "Put 'em there, partner. "
"물론이죠!" 이렇게요
Or "You bet!"
매장을 다니면서..
Walk on back to the back...
물론이죠
You bet.
말씀 고맙습니다, 에밋씨
Thanks for the
tips, Emmett.
존 케이시 때문에
무서워 죽겠다
Yup. John Casey
scares me.
그거야 네가 그렇게
꾹꾹 참으니까 그러지
Well, that's what happens
when you bottle up
your feelings like that.
그러다 언제 한번
뻥 터진다고
You wake up one day and
you're a seething mass of pain.
알았어
근데 질하고는 어때?
Right. Hey, what's going
on with you and Jill?
응. 아픈데 콕 찌르네
Ah, yeah.
My, my pain.
Let's talk about that.
- 걔 어디갔어?
- 큰 집
- Where is she?
- Big house.
큰 집 샀다고
Bought a big house.
교도소 쪽에 있는
커다란 집 샀어
Bought a real big house
up the river.
예쁘겠네
Oh, that sounds
really pretty.
너네 둘이 끝난거 맞지?
You guys are, uh,
"done" done, right?
응. 다시 시작하려던게 아니고
Yeah, I mean, I just figured
out hanging out with Jill
예전 관계를 정리하려던거였어
- was more about closing a door than opening one.
- I get it. I get it.
알았어. 예전 애인하고
만날 수도 있지
Listen, the old flame can burn,
right? But I bet you, it made
어찌됐든 그덕에 누가 더
너한테 맞는 사람인지 알게 됐잖아
you even more sure who
the right girl is for you.
마침 섹시한 천사께서 전화하셨네
Ah, speak of the smoking
hot angel.
난 가볼게 / 응
- I'll get out of here.
- Yeah.
네, 새라
Hey, Sarah.
척, 글로벌 라운치
에이전시(GLA)라고 알아요?
Chuck, does
the Global Launch Agency
mean anything to you?
GLA요? 알죠
명왕성을 제외한
GLA? Sure, they've
sent probes
나머지 행성에
탐사용 로켓을 보냈던 곳이잖아요
to every planet
except Pluto.
명왕성이 더이상
행성이 아니긴 하지만
Although, Pluto's not officially
a planet anymore,
그래서 진짜 속상했는데
which really bums me out.
그래 맞아
That's true.
우주 캠프는 멋있는
애들만 가는데니까
Space camp is where
all the cool kids go.
그 외에도 NSA를 위해서
기밀 연구를 수행하고 있네
GLA also conducts
top secret research
for the NSA.
우리의 보안과 무기 추적 기술은
모두 거기서 개발한거야
Most of our surveillance
and weapons tracking technology is developed there.
연구소의 안전 기지 중 한 곳을 뚫으려는
We picked up intel that
someone might try to penetrate
시도가 있었다는 정보를 입수했네
one of the lab's
secure facilities.
여러분들이 기지를 감시하고
I want you and the Intersect
to surveil the facility.
내부에서 떠오르는 사람이
없는지 살펴보게
See if there's anyone inside
who you flash on.
벌써 새 임무인가요?
Another mission already?
바토스키, 무슨 문제 있나?
Is there a problem,
Mr. Bartowski?
아니요 아닙니다
No, no.
전 그냥, 휴식시간을
가지고 싶었거든요
No, I was just, you know,
I was kind of hoping
for some downtime.
장군님, 여기서부턴
저희가 알아서 하겠습니다
We'll take it from here, ma'am.
휴식이 필요하셔?
Aw, you need a little break,
Bartowski?
네. 그랬음 좋겠어요
Yeah, that'd be nice.
질이 풀크럼 요원이라는게
저한텐 충격적이었다고요
I mean, finding out
Jill was Fulcrum
was a bit of a shock
to the system, you know?
그래서 마음을 정리할
시간이 좀 필요해요
I guess I wouldn't mind
some time
to sort out my feelings.
물론이지
Sure thing, Chuck.
내가 범죄자하고
스파이한테 전화해서
I'll just call all the criminals and rogue spies
척 바토스키가 마음을 정리할
and let
them know to hold on a sec,
시간이 필요하다고
잠시만 기다리라고 할게
'cause Chuck Bartowski
needs some time to sort out his lady feelings.
케이시, 그만해
Ease up, Casey.
척, 우리도 이게 얼마나
힘든 일인지 알아요
Look, Chuck, we know how hard
this has been for you,
하지만 다시 일을 하는게
도움이 많이 될지도 몰라요
but maybe a new mission is
exactly what you need right now.
밴에서 감시나 하고 있으라니
참 잘됐네
Great, new mission
in the surveillance van.
아이 신나라
Very exciting.
다 들려요, 척
You're on an open mic, Chuck.
그래요? 몰랐어요
Am I? That's, that's
good to know.
알려줘서 고마워요
Thanks for telling me that.
입구와 출입구 모두 안전해요
Uh, I have all the entrances
and exits covered.
아무 일 없는 것 같아요
It looks pretty quiet.
뭐 떠오른건 없고요?
You're not seeing anything?
네 전혀요
아무것도 없어요
Nothing. No flashes, nothing.
여기도 이상 없어요
I'm all clear here.
이상 무
All clear.
여기도 안전해
Security's tight.
척, 서쪽 문 폐쇄해!
Close the west lab door, Chuck!
네! 알겠어요!
시간이 좀 걸릴거예요!
I'm in! I'm in! I'm in, it's
just going to take a second.
어서 해! 빨리!
Do it! Do it!
네. 거의 다했어요
다 해가요
Almost got it. Almost got it.
Almost there.
어서, 척!
닫으라고!
Now, Chuck. Close it.
폐쇄해!
Lock it down!
소리 지르는거 듣는거
좋아하는 사람 아무도 없거든요!
You know, I don't know
one person
who responds positively
- to being yelled at!
- He's getting away, Chuck.
척, 이러다 빠져나가겠어!
다 했어요. 폐쇄했어요
됐죠?
Door closed.
Got it. There. See?
이 멍청아!
You idiot!
그 시스템 쓸 줄 안다며!
You said you knew
how to work this system.
잠시만요
Ooh, hang in there.
서둘러, 척
Come on, Chuck!
거의 다 했어요
다해가요
Almost got it.
열었어요
Got it.
고맙긴요
No problem.
날 좀 믿어보세요
Ye of little faith.
스승님?
Sensei?
출발해!
GO!
NSA 전술 지도자, 타이 베넷
NSA TACTICAL INSTRUCTOR
TY BENNETT
이런
Oh, no.
케이시, 얼굴 제대로 봤어?
Hey, did you get
a good look at him?
그럴 필요도 없었어
아는 사람이야
Didn't have to.
I know him.
뭐?
What?
새라, 케이시!
방금 그 사람 떠올랐어요
Guys! Hey! I just
flashed on that dude.
말도 안돼요
정말 세상 좁네요
And it is crazy,
it's actually
kind of a small world,
funny story.
그만해
Save it.
이름은 타이 베넷
His name's Ty Bennett.
내 스승님이야
He was my sensei.
내가 아는 모든걸
가르쳐주신 분이야
Taught me everything I know.
괜찮으십니까?
You okay?
Hmm.
BUY MORE
이젠 좀 낫군
Feeling better now.
네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)
영어자막 www.shooter.cn
싱크편집 / 한글번역
김호정(hojeong_@nate.com)
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON NBC : 2008/12/01
척! 척! 나 좀 도와줘
긴급 상황이야
Chuck! Chuck! You've got to
help me! This is an emergency!
- 척!
- 왜? 무슨 일이야!
- Chuck!
- What? What? What?
- 누나 누나! 괜찮아?
- 아니 안 괜찮아
- Ellie! Ellie! Ellie! Are you okay!?
- No! No!
데븐네 부모님께서
우리 놀래켜주신다고
Devon's parents decided to take the red-eye in
from Connecticut to surprise us!
코네티컷에서 야간 비행기 타고 오신대
누나때문에 놀라 죽을뻔했잖아
You scared the heck out of me.
난 또 누가 죽기라도
하는 줄 알았어
I thought this
was life or death.
맞아! 완벽한 집에서
완벽한 세 형제를 키운
It is! These are
two perfect parents that raised
완벽한 부모님이 오시는데
three perfect boys
in a perfect house,
- 집이 돼지우리 같잖아
- 걱정마
- and this place is a pigsty.
- Don't worry.
밤새 비행기 타셨으니깐
오시면 주무시고 싶어하실거야
We have time to clean up.
If they flew all night,
그니까 청소할
시간은 충분히 있잖아
they're going to want
to sleep all morning.
장난해? 부전자전이라고
데븐이랑 똑같아
Are you kidding me? The
awesome apple doesn't fall
far from the awesome tree.
난 그냥..
금방 갈게
I'm just going to...
I'll be right there.
???
짱인데!
이제야 일어났네
Awesome!
There's the man!
안녕하세요. 잘 오셨어요
두분 모두 근육질이시고
Wow! Welcome! Hi.
You guys are very muscular.
깨 계시네요!
And... and awake!
척, 데븐 부모님이셔
Chuck, this is
Devon's mom and dad.
우드콤 선생님
Drs. Woodcomb,
마침내 만나뵙네요
so nice to finally meet you.
우리 가족끼린
악수 같은거 안해요
Oh, no handshakes
in this family.
- 허니라고 불러요
- 네 허니
- You just call me Honey.
- Okay, Honey.
- 난 우디라고 불러주게
- 안녕하세요, 우디
- I'm Woody.
- Hey, Woody.
우리 아버진 항상 말씀하셨지
Yeah. My father
always said,
형편없는 애칭이
사람을 만든다고 말이야
"A terrible nickname
builds character. "
물론 데븐은
이상한 닉네임은 없지만
Of course, Devon wasn't into nicknames.
어서 너희들 결혼식을
준비하고 싶구나
I just can't
wait to start planning your dream wedding.
이미 준비하신 것 같은데요
Wow! It looks
like you already have.
아참, 척
Oh, and, Chuck,
출장요리사가 음식 샘플을 가지고
오늘 밤에 집에 오기로 했어요
the caterer is
bringing over
a sample menu tonight
for Devon and Ellie to decide what they like.
We hope you
여자친구하고 같이 오세요
and your... girlfriend
can join us.
네, 그럼요. 올 거예요
Yes! Of course!
Of course!
- 새라가 음식을 좋아하거든요
- 그렇답니다
- Sarah loves food.
- That she does!
네 참석할게요
So, yeah,
we'll be there!
잘됐군 잘됐어
Good. Good.
결혼식 준비까지 도와주시고
정말 감사해요. 그렇지 엘리?
So nice of you guys
to help us plan
the wedding. Right, Ell?
그렇고말고
Oh, absolutely!
어머니께서 이미 손님 명단에
장소에 색깔 파레트까지..
Your mom's already been busy
with all these lists of guests,
locations,
color palettes...
데븐이 네게 청혼한 다음부터
저렇게 신나있단다
She's been
so excited
ever since Devon
asked you to marry him.
네가 우리 가족이 되서
얼마나 기쁜지 몰라
I can't tell you
how happy we are
to welcome you
into our family.
이젠 척 자네도
우리 가족인거야
And now, you're stuck
with us, too, Chuck.
주먹이 정말 세시네요
You're very strong,
and have fists.
고맙습니다, 우드콤 선생님
Thank you, Dr. Woodcomb.
우디라니깐
"Woody. "
그럴게요
Okay.
아버지, 복근운동 하러 가요
Dad, let's go do our abs.
- 그래
- 운동하고 계세요
- Ooh, yeah.
- You guys do abs.
전.. 가서
확 죽어버릴래요
I'm... I'm just going to go...
kill myself.
타이 베넷, 가라데의 대가
Ty Bennett: karate master,
쿵푸 전문가, 실력있는 전략 전술가로
kung fu expert,
master strategist.
우리 훈련 시설 지도자 출신으로
A former instructor at our
training facility. And, today,
현재, 수배령이 내려진
부패 요원 중 한 명이네
one of our most wanted
rogue agents.
케이시, 스승님이
나쁜놈이네요
Dude, your sensei is a badass!
스승님 아니야
반역자일뿐이지
He's not my sensei.
He's a traitor.
나도 베넷 얘긴 들었지만
Wow. I've heard of Bennett,
그 사람한테 훈련받은 사람을
만난건 처음이야
but I've never met anyone
who actually trained with him.
그 얘긴 못해
기밀 사항이야
I can't talk about it.
It's classified.
어차피 이번 작전 때문에
베넷의 파일을 열어볼거야
We're opening Bennett's file
for this assignment.
자네가 개인적으로 알고 있는게 임무
성공에 중요한 역할을 할 수도 있네
Any personal knowledge you have
could be vital to the success of this mission.
말해봐요 케이시
우리도 좀 알려줘요
Come on, Casey.
Share with us.
지옥에서 알려주지
장군님
In hell.
General, if I may, why wasn't
I told that Bennett went rogue?
왜 제가 베넷이 배신했단걸
이제야 안거죠?
타이 베넷은 자신의 옛 제자들을
스카웃 해왔네
Ty Bennett has been recruiting
his former students.
정말 그 제자들이
제안을 받아들였나요?
He's actually turning agents?
베넷은 자신이 소집한 팀과 함께
With the team he's assembled,
물건을 훔치고
국제 암시장에 다시 되팔아왔어
Bennett has been extremely
effective at stealing weapons
and reselling them
on the global black market.
GLA에서는 뭘 훔쳐간거죠?
What did he steal from GLA?
관성 유도 장치야
An advanced
inertial guidance system.
적어도 무기는 아니네요
Well, that's not a weapon.
미사일에 붙이면
무기가 되지 멍청아
Well, fit sure looks like one when it's put in a missile,
moron.
있죠, 매번 멍청이라고 할때마다
You know,
when you call me moron,
제 맘이 다치거든요
that hurts me on the inside.
네가 그 문을 못 열어서
베넷을 놓친거야
Bennett got away because
you couldn't open a door.
다친게 네 맘 뿐이라는게
다행인줄이나 알아
You're lucky your feelings aren't the only
thing that got hurt.
사실 난 밴에 앉아서
떠올리기만 하면 되는거였어요
Technically,
I only have to sit in the van and flash.
왜 그래요
Hey.
그만해요
Guys.
베넷이 GLA 기술을 구매자에게 넘길
장소를 알아냈네
Gentlemen, we have intel pinpointing the location
where Bennett plans
to transfer the GLA technology
to his buyer.
시미 밸리에 있는
건설 현장이야
It's a construction site
in Simi Valley.
자네들이 그 거래를 막고
다시 유도 장치를 가져오게
I want you to stop the deal
and recover the guidance system.
알겠습니다
We're on it.
장군님. 이번 작전에 척이
참여하는게 안전할지 모르겠습니다
You know, I wonder if it's safe
for Chuck to go on this mission.
예측할 수 없는 변수들이
너무 많습니다
Too many unforeseeable
variables.
이런 상황에 척이 있으면
불리할 뿐입니다
In situations like this, he
has proven himself a liability.
자네 말이 맞네, 케이시
I think you're right, Casey.
척, 이번 작전에선 빠지게
Chuck, you will
be sitting this one out.
네? 잠시만요
What? Wait a minute.
뭔갈 떠올려야 할지도 모르잖아요
You might... you might need me
to flash on something.
우리나라는 인터섹트없이도
Oh, this country
has gotten
200년이나 잘 살았어
by for 200 years
without an Intersect.
너 없어도 괜찮을거야
I'm sure we'll
be just fine.
왜, 상처 받았어?
What? Did I hurt your feelings?
기분 상하게 하고 싶진 않지만
I've tried to spare
your feelings,
더 열심히 해야합니다 여러분
but the gloves
are coming off, people.
바이모어의 오래된 전통을
다시 시작하려고 해요
I've decided
to reinstitute a time-honored
Buy More tradition.
수요일마다 코맨도하기
Commando Wednesdays.
그 전통은 끝난적이 없어
That tradition
never stopped.
바로 오늘부터
From this day on,
우리 지점에서는
this branch will hold-
뭘까요
wait for it-
이 달의 우수직원
콘테스트를 열겠습니다
an Employee of the Month
contest.
신나지 않습니까?
Oh! Isn't that exciting?
네, 신나는거 꾹 참고 있습니다
I can barely contain myself,
sir.
다들 고객의 소리 카드는
알고 계시겠죠
I assume you're all aware of our
customer
comment cards.
매달 여러분의 점수를 기록해서
승자를 결정하겠습니다
Each month, we will
tally your score and select a winner.
자네나 자네
He or she
누구든지
or whomever
이기는 사람에겐 8x10 크기의 멋진 사진을
will not only get
an 8 X 10 glossy photo
바이모어의 창업자시자
CEO이신
right beside Moses Finkelstein,
EMPLOYEE OF THE MONTH
YOUR NAME HERE
모세스 핑글스틴 씨
옆에 붙이도록 하겠습니다
the CEO and founder of Buy More,
거기에 또
but there will be
특별상이 있을겁니다
a bonus prize!
최선을 다해서
이기시길 바랍니다
May the best employee win.
척, 우수 직원 콘테스트
어떻게 할 생각이야?
Okay, so how are feeling
about this
about this whole
Employee-of-the-Month thing?
Um, you know what?
Whatever, Morgan.
있잖아
알게 뭐야, 모건
난 별로 관심없어
I don't, I don't really care.
우린 관심없다
알겠어
We don't care. Roger that.
Hey.
지금쯤 벌써 출발했을줄
알았는데요
I thought you guys
would already be gone.
내가 필요한거죠
인정해요 맞죠?
Admit it.
You need me, don't ya?
그냥 괜찮은지 보러 온거예요
I came to make sure
you're okay.
그거 보려고 감시카메라
설치한거 아니예요?
Well, isn't that what all the surveillance
cameras are for?
척, 난 케이시가 한 얘기에
동의하지 않아요
Listen, I don't agree
with Casey
that you would be a liability
on this mission.
케이시가 좀 지나쳤어요
He was out of line.
걱정마요. 다 이해해요
Don't worry. I get it.
내가 질 때문에 힘들어하는게
He thinks I let my feelings
for Jill
임무에 방해가 될거라 생각하는거잖아요
get in the way
of the mission.
하지만 그건 아니예요
앞으로 그런 일 없을거예요
But he's wrong.
I would never do that...
다시는요
...again.
척
Listen, Chuck,
이건 당신 때문이 아니라
케이시 때문이예요
this isn't about you,
it's Casey.
케이시는 베넷과
오랜 기간 훈련했어요
Casey trained with Bennett
for a long time,
그러다보면
서로 신뢰가 쌓이잖아요
and when you have a mentor
like that,
a real trust develops
between you,
케이시는 배신감을 느끼는거예요
and Casey feels betrayed.
힘들다는거 알지만
I know it's hard,
케이시를 조금만 이해해주세요
but maybe you could
cut him some slack.
네. 어떤 기분일지
알 것 같네요
Yeah, I guess I know
how that feels.
THROUGH THESE HALLS WALK
THE SMARTEST EMPLOYEES IN THE WORLD
SALES TEAM
자 확실히 해두자
이 달의 우수 직원
All right, just to be absolutely
clear, our position on
일에 우린 관심 없는거야
Employee of the Month
is that we don't care,
다들 알았지?
Are you guys with me?
알았어
쥐꼬리만큼도 관심 없음
Yep, not caring.
Not a rat's ass.
눈꼽만큼도 없음
Not a fat
and/or hairy one.
잠깐
근데 왜 관심 없는건데?
Wait. Why don't we care again?
왜냐하면 우수 직원
그 얘긴 다 사기고
Because Employee of
the Month is a scam.
열심히 일하는건
멍청이들이나 하는 짓이니까
And working hard
is for suckers.
생각해봐
Think about it.
열심히 일하면
실적이 오르겠지
You work hard,
sales go up.
실적이 오르면
주주들이 돈을 벌어
Sales go up,
shareholders get rich.
주주들은 돈이라도 벌지
우린 대체 뭘 얻는데?
Shareholders get rich,
and we get what exactly?
에밋이 무슨 상이
있다고 했잖아
He said something about a prize.
모세스 핑클스틴 옆에
사진 붙여주는거?
Your face on a wall
next to Moses Finkelstein?
됐어 필요없어
No, thank you, no.
그 상은 꼭두각시나 다름없다고
You know what?
Keep your stupid stooge prize.
우린 아무것도
못 얻는단 말이야?
So we get nothing?
에밋이 공을 다 차지할거야
Emmett's gonna get
all the credit.
승진까지 할지도 모르지
He may even get a promotion.
그리고 그 다음엔?
And then guess what?
갑자기 우리 보스가
될지도 모른다고
One day, he's gonna be the boss.
그래서 그 다음엔?
So then what?
에밋이 바이모어를
끔찍하게 만들어 버릴거라고?
Then Emmett turns the Buy More
into a nightmare of pain
and suffering?
해결책이 하나 있어
There is a solution.
말해봐 빨리
Tell it,
tell it.
우리끼리 콘테스트를 열자
We have our own contest,
우리끼리 따로
a side bet.
누가 고객의 소리에서
최저점을 받는지 말이야
We see who can get
the lowest score
on their comment cards.
에밋이 원하는 정반대로 하는거야
We beat Emmett at his own game.
진짜 똑똑하다
Pure genius.
지금부터는
From now on,
손님들이 알아서 사라고 해
the customers can go
service themselves.
제프리, 다시 말하면
그냥 관심 끄라는거야
In the retail sense,
Jeffrey.
Don't get any ideas.
베넷은 안 나타날거야
Bennett will never show.
어째서?
Why?
멍청하지 않으니까
He's too smart
for this.
번호판 보여?
You get a read on the plates?
케이시. 그냥 척 부르자
뭔가 떠올릴지도 모르잖아
Look, Casey, just call Chuck.
Maybe he'll flash on it
그럼 상대가 누군지도 알 수있고
and we'll know
who we're dealing with.
걔 없이 우리끼리 해
I think I'll take my
chances without him.
알았어
Oh, all right.
하면 되잖아
Fine.
여보세요?
Hello?
나야. 방금 사진 하나 보냈어
Hey, we just sent you an image
of a van.
번호판 보고
떠오르는게 있나 봐
Take a look at the plates,
see if you flash on it.
네 알겠어요 그럴게요
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, of course.
물론이죠
도움이 될 수 있다면요
Absolutely.
Whatever I can do to help.
케이시 아직 안 왔어요
You know, I don't have it yet.
고해상도 사진이라 그런가봐요
It's probably
a high-resolution photo.
게다가 여기선 가끔 3G 연결이
잘 안되거든요
And my 3G connection gets
interference in here sometimes.
너드 허드 어쩌고는 관심없으니까
빨리 보기나해
Spare me the Nerd Herd crap.
Get on it.
정보가 필요해, 지금 당장
If there's intel,
we need it now!
저번엔 미국 정부가 인터섹트 없이도
Hey, I thought you said
the U.S. government got by
무사히 200년이나 지냈다면서요?
just fine for 200 years
without the Intersect?
내 말 잘 들어
이 하찮은 놈..
Listen, you insignificant
little puke...
임무 수행중이지
You're on a mission.
베넷 쪽 사람들한테
둘러쌓여있을지도 몰라
Maybe surrounded
by Bennett's men.
받아라 어서 어서
Pick up, pick up, pick up,
pick up.
내 전화 끊었냐?
Did you hang up on me?
아니요 말도 안되죠
그런 짓을 왜 하겠어요
No, that's crazy talk.
I would never do that.
지금 여기가 연결이 별로 안 좋아서..
It's a bad connection
that I had with the...
잠시만요. 사진 빨리 볼게요
Hold on. Let me just look
at the picture real quick.
미안해요. 아무것도 안 떠올라요
I got nothing. Sorry, no flash.
시간 낭비해줘서 고맙다
Thanks for wasting my time.
여보세요?
Hello?
케이시. 저기 구매자야
Hey, that's the buyer.
시간이 없어
We're out of time.
예전 방식대로 해야겠는데
Looks like we do this
the old-fashioned way.
준비됐어?
- Okay? Go.
- Yeah.
차 밖으로 나와!
어서 나와!
Get out of the car!
Out of the car!
차 가지세요
경찰 절대 안 부를게요
Take the car, man,
and I won't call the cops.
차 위에 손 얹어!
어서 올려!
Hands on the car!
Put 'em on the car!
넌 누구야?
Who the hell are you?
전 운전사예요
I'm a driver. I'm here to pick
손님을 태워서
이걸 전달해주기로 했어요
up a passenger
and give them that.
베넷 짓이야
뛰어! 어서!
Bennett. Run! Go! Go!
실례합니다
존 케이시를 만나러 왔는데요
Excuse me.
Can you tell me where
I can find John Casey?
제가 그 친구 물건을 갖고 있어서요
I have something
that belongs to him.
존 케이시라..
...Casey,
존 케이시라고 하셨죠?
you say? John Casey?
잠시 뒤에 가서
있는지 보고 올게요
You know, I'm gonna go
to the back
and-and-and check
on that for you.
빨리..다녀올게요
So let me just... do that...
quick.
전화 좀 받아요, 존
좀 받으라고요 케이시
Pick up the phone, John.
Pick up the phone, Casey!
케이십니다
This is Casey.
코드 레드! 코드 레드!
더 더 빨개요!(Red)
Code Red! Code Red!
Redder than red!
진짜 빨개요!
이렇게 빨갈수가 없다고요!
It is the reddest!
It is the reddest of all hues!
데프콘 1인가 5인가 그거예요
We are Defcon One, or Five
아무튼 서둘러요 빨리!
or whichever means "Hurry,"
right now!
베넷이 바이모어에 와 있어요
Bennett is at the Buy More!
이런 안돼
Oh, no.
존 케이시를 찾고 있는데요
I'm looking for John Casey.
어디 가면 만날 수 있죠?
Can you tell me where
to find him?
제가 안내 데스크처럼 보여요?
What do I look like,
an information desk?
뭐라고요?
Excuse me?
네 그럼요. 가 보세요
(Excuse me의 여러가지 뜻을 가지고 한 말)
Yes, fine, you're excused.
아참 나가는 길에
고객의 소리 쓰시는거 잊지 마시고요
Oh, and don't forget to fill out a customer comment card
on your way out.
현자는 낯선 사람에게도
항상 존중을 해주죠
Wise man always
treats a stranger with respect,
그 낯선 사람이
적이 될지도 모르니까요
for he could be gazing
on the face of an enemy.
손님
죄송합니다 죄송합니다
Hi. Sorry, sorry.
확인해보고 오느라고요
I just checked into
it, sir,
그리고 존 케이시는
오늘 비번이라 없고요
and John Casey
is unfortunately not
working today, and I don't know
when he's gonna be back in,
언제 출근할진 잘 모르겠네요
다음주에 다시 한번 와주세요
but you could try back
next week.
화요일쯤에요
Uh, maybe, maybe Tuesday-ish.
고맙습니다
Thank you.
천만에요
You're welcome.
저 남자 짱이야!
That guy was awesome!
방금 이 캔으로
하는거 봤어?
Dude, did you see
what he did to this can?
맨손으로 이렇게 해놨다니까
He did this
with his bare hands.
이렇게 뭉개버렸어
얼굴에 하면 어떻게 될지 상상이나 돼?
Crush, like that.
Could you imagine what he could do to a guy's face?
지금 말할 기분 아니다
Not feeling very
chatty right now.
케이시 잠시만요
끊지 말아봐요
Hold on, Casey, don't hang up.
케이시 스승님이 여기 있어요
I'm looking right at
your sensei.
베넷이 바이모어에 있다고?
Bennett's at the Buy More?
뭐? 어떻게 그게 가능해?
What? How is that possible?
있었어요. 지금은 아니고요
Was. Was at the Buy More.
지금은 라지 마트 주차창 건물에 있어요
제가 미행중이예요
Now he's in the Large Mart
parking garage. I'm tailing him.
그만둬 이 멍청아!
너가 덤빌 상대가 아니야
No, stop, imbecile!
You're no match for him.
바보같은 짓 하지마
Don't be an idiot!
케이시, 지금 이게 다
상처받아서 이러는거예요
Look, you're only reacting
like this
because your own feelings were
hurt, okay?
나한테 화내지 말아요
Please don't lash out at me.
어디로 갔지?
Where did he go?
엄마야
Oh, God!
척
Chuck?
척!
Chuck?!
베넷이 알아챈거야
지금쯤 죽었을지도 몰라
Bennett's got him.
He's probably dead by now.
닥치고 운전이나 해
Shut up and drive!
제가 커서
여기 들어가긴 좀 힘든데
I'm a little tall for something
like this.
다른 곳에 앉으면 안될까요?
Is there another seating option,
perhaps?
엘리, 바이모어에서
물건 등록해도 괜찮겠어?
Ell, are you sure
you're okay registering
for a wedding here
at the Buy More?
자기 부모님이 원하시잖아
Whatever your parents want.
진공 포장기가 필요 없다고
생각할지도 모르겠지만
You think you may not need
a vacuum sealer,
갑작스럽게 외과 과장님하고
남편분이서
but suddenly the Chief of
Surgery is coming over
연어 산적요리를 가져오신거야
with her husband
for salmon kabobs,
어때, 이거 덕에 토요일 파티가
일요일 소풍처럼 변하는거지
and voila, Saturday's party
turns into Sunday's picnic.
이것도 할까요?
왜 안되겠어요?
Why not? Can't hurt?
어머 캠코더네
Ooh, camcorder.
첫날밤에 손주가 생겼으면 좋겠구나
Ah, first for the honeymoon,
then the grandkids.
아버지!
Dad!
그만하세요
Crossing the line.
무슨 말하기 전에
Before you say
anything,
위압적이신거 나도 알아
그냥 좋으셔서 그래
I know they're coming on strong,
but they're just really excited.
자기가 부모님하고
연락 안하는거 아시고 그러는거야
They know your parents
aren't around.
괜찮아. 다 도와주시려고
그러시는거 알아
That's fine. I know that they're
just trying to help.
그리고
두분 다 짱이신데 뭘
And you know, they're,
they're awesome.
레스터, 척 봤어?
Hey, Lester,
you seen Chuck?
아마도요
Maybe.
이 근처에 있어?
So, is he around?
몰라요. 그럴수도요
Don't know. Could be.
좀 찾아줄래?
Can you find him for me?
네 그럼요
그럴수야 있죠
Yeah, sure, I could,
하지만 스스로 찾으시는게
더 좋지 않겠어요?
but, uh, wouldn't that be more
fulfilling for you
if you did it yourself?
미안해요. 말 같지도 않은
콘테스트 때문에 그래요
Look, I'm so sorry.
It's a stupid store contest.
찾아볼게요
대신에 제가 도와준거
I can help you,
but do me a solid
이 카드에 적으시면 안돼요
and do not mention it
on this card.
알았죠?
고마워요
Yes? Thank you, buddy.
TRACKING: LOCKED
시계에서 오는 신호가
점점 강해져
The signal from
the watch
is getting stronger.
Chuck's close.
이 근처에 있는거야
케이시, 뭐하는거야?
Casey, what are you doing?
빅토리아는 견뎌낼 수 있을거야
The vic can take the hit.
안돼 좋지 않아
좋지 않아
Oh, no, not good, not good.
잠깐
척 찾았어
Wait. I've got Chuck.
신호가..
It says the signal is...
신호가 우리 바로 앞에서 와
the signal is right
in front of us.
안돼 케이시 멈춰 어서!
척이 저 안에 있어!
No, Casey, stop, stop!
Chuck's in the car!
이러다 척이 죽겠어!
You're gonna kill Chuck!
빨라. 너무 너무 빨라
Oh, fast. And he's driving very,
very fast.
케이시!
Casey!
여기 생각보다
그렇게 안 좁아요
It's actually more spacious
in here than you might think.
이봐!
Hey!
꼼짝마!
Freeze!
존, 이렇게 보니 반갑군
John, it's good to see you.
머리에 손 올려
Keep your hands on your head.
함정에서 살아남았군
아주 잘했어
You survived my trap.
Very good.
무릎 꿇어
Get on your knees.
난 자네가 하는 일들을 지켜봤어
I followed your career, John.
자넨 바스당 분파의
고문에서도 살아남았고
(아랍의 민족주의 정당)
You survived torture
at the hands of Baath separatists.
아프가니스탄에선 2년간
첩보 활동을 했지
You did two years undercover
in Afghanistan.
내가 없었다면
그게 가능했겠나?
Could you have done
any of that without me?
아니
No.
당연히 아니지
Of course not.
자넨 내 훈련덕에 살아남은거야
My training saved you.
제안할게 있어서 왔어
I came here
to ask you something.
다시 내 제자가 되거라
Be my student again.
다음 단계로 넘어갈 수 있게
훈련을 받아
Take your training
to the next level.
그게 다야?
That's it?
그거밖에 못해?
That's all you got?
다른 사람들도 이렇게 해서
넘어갔나?
That's how
you're turning the others?
헛소리 집어쳐
난 반역자가 아니야
Save your breath.
I'm no traitor.
확실히 내가 실수를 했군
Obviously,
I made a mistake.
자넨 내 팀에
들어올 실력이 못 돼
You aren't good enough
for my team.
베넷!
Hey!
그래서 베넷을 놓쳤다는거군
So Bennett got away.
또 다시
Again.
그런 일이 있는 동안
인터섹트는 어디에 있었지?
If you don't mind me asking,
where was the Intersect
during all of this?
사실 전
베넷 차 트렁트 안에 있었는데요
Well, technically
I was in Bennett's trunk,
그래서 아무것도 못 봤는데
소리는 재밌는것 같더라고요
so I didn't see anything
that happened,
but it sounded
very exciting.
잠깐
소령, 그렇다면
Wait. So, Major,
자네가 그 무모한 싸움을 하는동안
while you were playing
your game of chicken,
척은 베넷의 차
트렁크 안에 있었단 말이야?
Chuck was in Bennett's trunk?
인터섹트의 안전을 확보한 후엔
As soon as we
ascertained
케이시 소령도 중지했습니다
the Intersect's location,
Major Casey disengaged.
자네와 베넷 모두 이 일을
Sounds like Bennett has decided
개인적인 일로 생각하는 모양이니
to make this personal, Casey,
and so have you.
- 자넬 이번 임무에서 제외하겠네
- 죄송합니다만..
- I'm pulling you off the case.
- With all due respect...
이럴까봐 베넷이 배신한걸
얘기하지 않은거야
This is why I didn't tell you
about Bennett.
자네가 이렇게 복수하겠다고
달려들줄 알았네
I knew you would turn it
into a vendetta.
자네 뒤치다꺼리는
다른 팀에게 시키도록 하지
I'm bringing in another team to clean up your mess.
하지만 제가 베넷이 어떻게
행동하는지 알지 않습니까
But I know Bennett.
I know how he operates.
자네의 주요 임무는 인터섹트를
보호하는 일이란걸 잊지말게
You're forgetting
your primary objective is protecting the Intersect.
이번 작전이 완료될 때까지
기지에 남아있게
You will remain in Castle until the mission is completed.
휴식기간이라 생각하게
Consider it
a cooling-off period.
너 이 자식..
You little...
일이 이렇게 될지 몰랐어요
I didn't know this was
going to happen.
몰랐어요. 새라 빨리
나 몰랐다고 해줘요
I didn't know... tell him I didn't
know this was going to happen!
내 주요 임무는
널 보호하는게 아니야
If my primary objective
wasn't to protect you...I KILL YOU.
죽이는거지
말도 안돼
I can't believe it.
날 이 작전에서 뺀건 월권이야
Beckman was out of line pulling
me off this mission.
장군님 말이 맞아
I agree with her.
넌 지금 너무 감정적이야
You're too emotionally involved.
척한테 푹 빠져사는
사람이 그게 할 소리냐
This from the agent that
can't keep her chocolate out of Bartowski's
peanut butter.
척에 대한 내 감정이 어떻든간에
Whatever my feelings
may be for Chuck,
난 알면서도 척을
위험에 빠뜨린적은 없어
I never knowingly endangered the asset.
베넷한테 진 응어리 때문에
You let your anger
판단력이 흐려진거야
toward Bennett cloud
your judgment.
드디어 척한테 마음 있는거 인정했네
You finally admit that you do
have feelings for the nerd.
아니. 내가 인정할건
나한테 마음이란게 있다는거 뿐이야
No, all I will admit to
is having feelings.
이 쪽에서 20년 일하면서
한가진 확실하게 알았어
20 years in the business
has taught me one sure thing-
사람들.. 사람들은
결국엔 우릴 실망시킨다는거야
that people...
people let you down in the end.
그래. 네가 무슨 생각인지
잘 들었어
Well, it's nice to know
where we stand.
케이시랑 얘기해봤어요?
Did you talk to Casey?
화났어요?
Is he mad?
마음이 안 좋아요
I feel horrible.
케이시야 항상 화나있죠
원래 그러잖아요
Casey is always mad.
That's his baseline.
장군님 앞에서
그런 말을 하는게 아니였어요
I never should have said
all that stuff in front of the general.
아니예요
맞는 말 했어요
No, your assessment
was accurate.
사실은 사실이잖아요
I mean, the facts
are the facts.
알아요 하지만
케이시가 맘 고생이 심하잖아요
True, but the guy's
going through a lot.
제가 정말 친구였다면
If I were really a friend,
I would look past
케이시가 어떤 말을 했는지
기분은 어떨지 생각했어야해요
what he's saying and remember
how he's feeling.
지금 어떤 일을 겪고 있는지
I mean, I should know
better than anybody
내가 누구보다
더 잘 알아야 하잖아요
what he's going through
right now.
척. 정말 자상하네요
Chuck, you're so sweet.
하지만 사과 한다고 해도
풀리지 않을거예요
But, you know, an apology
is not going to work,
케이시는 항상
전투 태세라
because Casey is combat ready
at all times.
무슨 말을 해도
들리지 않을거예요
Which means his feelings
are liabilities.
새라도 항상
전투 태세여야하는거 아니예요?
Well, aren't you supposed
to be combat ready at all times?
일 끝나고 집에서 만나요
I'll meet you at your
sister's wedding tasting after your Buy More shift.
그리고
아래층엔 내려가지 마세요
And please,
don't go downstairs.
케이시 혼자 두세요
Leave Casey alone.
트위들디, 트위들덤
If it isn't
Tweedledee, Tweedledum
트위들더머
and... Tweedledumber.
다들 축하드려요
Oh, congratulations
goes out to you.
왜요, 저희가
1등이라도 했나요?
What do we win,
a prize or something?
이 침체된 매장의
무능한 직원들 중에서도
Well, of all the incompetent
employees in this backwater branch,
여러분 셋이
눈에 띄는 기록을 세웠더군요
you three have
distinguished yourselves-
역사상 최저 고객 평가
점수를 받으셨어요
with the lowest
customer evaluation scores in recorded history.
그래요?
Really?
얼마나 낮은데요?
- What... how low exactly?
- Are we talking like
심하게 낮은가요 아님..
truly abysmal, or...?
당신 점수를 다 합쳐도
1점밖에 안돼요
Combined your highest score
was a one.
- 한번 덤벼봐, 임마
- 좋아
- Dare to dream, baby.
- All right.
여러분이 다들 이 콘테스트를
Well, since none of you
seem to be taking
진지하게 받아들이는 것 같지 않으니
this Employee of the Month
contest very seriously,
이젠 당근은 버리고
채찍을 써야겠군요
I must abandon the carrot,
and use my stick.
그거 불법 아니예요?
You sure that's legal?
최저점을 받은 직원은
지금부터
From now on, the employee
with the lowest scores
한달간 매주 토요일 밤에
가게 마감을 맡게 될겁니다
will close up
every Saturday night
- for an entire month.
- All right, stop.
저기 잠시만요
이러시면 안돼죠
You can't do this
to us, okay?
대체 왜 안되죠?
I'm sorry, I can't?
- 토요일은 신성한 날이니까요
- 저 안식일엔 일 못해요
- Saturday's are sacred.
- I can't work on Shabbat.
네
데이트 있단 말이예요
Yeah. It's date night.
빨래?
Laundry night?
- 둘다 하는 날이예요
- 시간 낭비 하지 맙시다
- It's two-for-one night.
- You're wasting time.
하루를 줄테니
점수를 올리세요
You have one night
to raise your scores.
빨리 시작하는게 좋을겁니다
You better get crackin'.
이거 제 직원 할인 카드인데요
This is my employee
discount card.
여기서 파는 모든 물건을
20% 할인 해드려요
It's good for 20% off
anything in the store. Go nuts.
나가시면서 저한테
좋은 말만 써주시면 돼요
Just put in a good word
for me on your way out.
아니요 꺼리다니요?
No, mind?
그게 무슨 말씀이세요?
Why would I mind?
제가 손님분을 위해서
다 실어드리고
Just let me get this puppy
loaded up for you
금방 돌아오겠습니다
and then I'll come right back
for sub...
별 4개?
Four stars?!
내가 겨우 별 4개 받으려고
당신한테 아부떤줄 알아?
I just kissed your ass
for four lousy stars?!
대체 뭘 더 어떻게 하라고!
What do you people
want from me!
앞으론 그냥 내 얼굴에
침을 뱉어!
Just spit in my
face next time!
안녕 제프
Hey, Jeff.
무슨 일이야?
괜찮아?
How's it going, man?
You all right?
고객 서비스가 뭔지
이젠 좀 알거같아
I think I'm getting the hang
of this customer service stuff.
ENTER
그렇지
Yeah...
ACCESS DENIED
여보세요 케이시
좀 어때요?
Casey, hey.
Hey, how you doing?
좀 내려와봐
Get down here.
전화줘서 고마워요
Um, look, I'm glad you called,
because I was actually going
안 그래도 전화해서
사과하려고 했는데
- to call you to say sorry... - I don't care
if it's your time of the month, Bartowski.
니가 그 날이라서
그런가보다 하고 넘어갔어
내려와봐
Get down here please.
그건.. 그건 안 될것 같아요
I don't...
I don't think I can.
새라가 내려가지 말랬어요
Sarah said not to.
잘 들어
Listen, buddy...
난 23살 때부터
베넷한테서 훈련받았어
I started training
under Ty Bennett
when I was 23 years old.
나도 그 땐 멍청했고
I was an idiot back then.
그 사람 훈련 받을만큼
실력이 안 됐는데도
I wasn't good enough
to qualify for his program,
베넷은 날 받아들여줬어
but he took me on anyway.
내가 아는건
다 그 사람한테서 배운거야
You know, so, he taught me
everything I know-
자기수양
self-discipline,
의리
duty.
어떻게 해야할지 모르겠어, 척
I don't know
what to think here, pal.
당황스러워
I'm feeling kind of exposed.
내 모든게 무너져버린 것 같아
I feel like my whole foundation
has been undermined here.
베넷은..
He was like, a...
전화론 얘기 못 하겠어
I can't talk about this
over the phone.
그럼요 그럼요
이런 얘기도 해주고 고마워요
No, no, I'm glad you're finally
opening up to me.
금방 갈게요
Be right there.
고마워 친구
Thanks, buddy.
Hey...
케이시 미안해요
최대한 빨리 왔어요
Hey, buddy, I'm sorry, I got
here as fast as I could.
그리고 아까 제가
하려고 했던 얘기 말인데요
And I wanted
to tell you seriously
what I was saying
on the phone earlier-
미안해요 케이시
I am sorry, man.
예전에 스승님과의 일은
사적인 일인데 제가..
I know, your sensei from the
past... it's very personal...
그렇지
- Yeah.
- Hey! Hey!
놔줘요
왜 이래요?
Let go.
What are you doing?
Oh, oh, gentle.
살살해요
자 인터섹트
떠올려
Now, Intersect, flash.
차 충돌 당시
감시 카메라 영상이야
This is the surveillance
footage from the crash.
케이시, 이런다고
될 일이 아니예요
Casey, it doesn't work
like that, okay?
그냥 번뜩 떠오르는게 아니라..
I can't just flash on cue...
네 알겠다고요
멀홀랜드 드라이브 1919번지
Okay, okay,
1919 Mulholland Drive.
무술 도장이고
It's a martial arts dojo,
베넷이 불법 행위를
숨기려고 만든 장소예요
but also a cover for
Bennett's illegal activity.
수고했어, 인터섹트
Good work, Intersect.
케이시, 지금이 휴식기라는건
알고 있는거죠
You know, I think
you should reconsider
this whole cooling-off period.
장군님께서 여기 남아있으라고
한건 다 이유가 있는..
I think General Beckman was
onto something when she said you
- should stay down here...
- Come on, I need that eyeball.
이리와. 눈 좀 쓰자
케이시
대체 무슨 일이예요?
Casey, what has
gotten into you?!
케이시답지 않게 대체 왜 이래요
What is going on? This is
totally uncharacteristic...
케이시가 명령에
불복종하는건 처음 봐요
I've never seen you
disobey an order.
뭐예요 미쳤어요?
정신이 나갔어요?
What are you, nuts,
crazy, out of your mind?
좋아요 됐어요
새라한테 전화할꺼예요
Okay, that's it-
I'm calling Sarah.
있잖아 척
You know what, Chuck?
내가 너한테 사과할게 있어
I think I might owe
you an apology now.
고마워요
That's very nice of you.
뭐가 미안한데요?
Huh? What's it for?
거짓말, 욕한거
내 감정가지고 장난친거?
The lying, the name-calling,
the emotional manipulation?
아니
이거 말이야
Nope. For this.
잠깐 안돼요 안돼
Wait, no, no.
안돼요 케이시 제발요
잠시만요 안돼요
No, Casey, no, no, no, wait,
wait wait. You don't understand.
오늘 밤에 누나 결혼식 때문에
저녁 먹기로 했단 말이예요
I have dinner with Ellie tonight and we're tasting food
for her wedding.
꼭 가야돼요
I can't miss it.
있지. 내가
베넷 밑에서 배울 때
You know, when I was
Bennett's student,
평정심을 유지하느라
고생이 많았지
I struggled with my calm.
내가 노여움이 지나치게 쌓여서
He said I held too much anger
and that made me weak.
그게 날 약하게 만든다더군
가끔 네 얼굴을 보고 있으면 말이야
Sometimes when I see
your face, Bartowski,
내 평정심이 확 그냥..
my calm center just wants to...
내가 어디가는지 말하기만 해
You tell anyone where I'm going,
이걸 박아줄테니까
and this is yours.
네?
What? Hey!
힘 좀 써봐
힘 좀 써, 척
Use the Force.
Use the Force, Chuck.
척 안왔는데
식사 시작해도 괜찮겠니?
So, you're sure it's all right
to start without Chuck?
- 걔가 원래 자주 늦어요
- 가끔 자기 세계에 푹 빠져서요
- Yeah, he has a tendency to run late.
- Yeah, it's like the kid's
in his own world
half the time.
힘들겠어요 새라
Must drive you crazy, Sarah.
아뇨, 이젠 익숙해요
Oh, I'm pretty
used to it, actually.
게다가 항상
그럴듯한 이유가 있어서요
And Chuck always
has a good excuse.
자 그럼 다들 동의한거지?
So we are all
in agreement then?
송어는 선택하고
Yes to the trout,
비프 오 쥬는 빼고
no to the beef au jus.
엘리
어떤 케익이 제일 맘에 들었니?
And what was
your favorite cake, Ellie?
- 전..
- 그건 상관없고
- Um...
- Oh, it doesn't matter.
- 레드 벨벳케익으로 하자
- 그거 좋아
- Let's agree on the red velvet.
- Big fan.
난 코스 사이에
샤벗 나오는게 좋던데
And I love sorbet
between courses.
좋은 생각이예요, 우디
Great idea, Woody.
그래, 머리는 위로 올릴거니?
So, are you going
to wear your hair up?
잠시만
Wait a second...
방금 좋은 생각이 떠올랐어
I just had
a brilliant idea.
흰색 넥타이
White ties.
우디한테 흰색 넥타이가
그렇게 잘 어울린단다
Woody looks so handsome
in a white tie.
- 너무 격식차린걸까?
- 잘 모르겠어요
- That's not too formal is it?
- I don't know.
네 아버지와 연락 안하고
지내는거 알아
And I know you're not
in contact with your dad,
결혼식 때 내 손 잡고
나갔으면 좋겠구나
so I would be honored, really,
to walk you down the aisle on your wedding day.
저기 우리 결혼식 얘기만 해요
You know, guys, maybe we should
just table the wedding talk.
아니, 아니야
Um, no.
정말 꼭 드리고 싶은
말씀이 있어요
I have something
I'd like to say, actually.
성대한 결혼식도 좋다고 했고
Um, I said yes to the big
wedding and I said yes
들러리 드레스를 버건디
오르간자로 하는것도 좋다고 했어요
to the burgundy organza
bridesmaid dresses,
하지만 더이상은 못하겠어요
and I just can't
say yes anymore.
죄송해요. 다들
도우려고 하시는건 알지만
And I'm sorry, I know that
you're trying to help,
제 대답은
싫다는거예요
but the answer is no.
죄송해요 죄송합니다
미안해
I'm sorry... I'm sorry,
I'm sorry.
엘리
Babe...
실례할게요
Sorry.
엘리
Sweetie...
자기야
sweetheart...
자기?
Sweetheart?
그래요 새라
Well, Sarah...
요거트 가게를 한다고 했던가요?
so you're in the yogurt game?
네
Yeah.
요거트 가게요
Yeah, yogurt.
자 제발 제발
Come on, baby.
Yeah, yeah.
그렇지
Yes.
우디 / 응?
- Woody...
- Huh?
애들끼리 얘기하게
우린 나가서 산책해요
I think we should go for a walk
and give the kids some time to themselves.
엘리 전화네
Oh, it's Ellie's phone.
척한테 왔어요
내가 받을까요?
Oh, it's Chuck.
Should I answer it?
제가 받을게요
고맙습니다
Oh, I'll take it.
Thank you.
여보세요 척
어디예요?
Hey, Chuck, where are you?
새라 새라
세상에 다행이다
Sarah, Sarah, thank God.
저기요
Listen, um...
케이시가 협박을 했어요
Casey threatened my life,
- 그니까 제 입으론 말 못해요
- 네?
- so technically I can't tell you...
- What?
그럼 맞춰봐요
맞춰보세요
Well, you could guess though.
Yeah, you could guess.
척, 게임할 시간 없어요
Chuck,
I don't have time for games.
어서 맞춰봐요!
Just guess!
맞는지 틀린지 알려줄게요
I'll tell you if you're
hot or cold.
그리고 참고로
And FYI,
여기 진짜 추워요
this place is very cold.
얼어 죽을거 같아요
It's... it's practically frozen.
오렌지 오렌지에 있군요
You're at Orange Orange.
네! 맞아요!
대단해요
Bingo! Yes, you're amazing!
맞춰볼까요
기지로 내려갔더니 케이시가
Let me guess- you went down
into the Castle and Casey
당신을 이용해서 빠져나가면서
오렌지 오렌지에 가두고
used you to get out and
then he locked you
in the Orange Orange and now
he's going after Bennett.
베넷을 쫓으러 갔다는거죠
진짜 대단하네요
어떻게 알았어요?
Wow. That's very impressive.
How did you...?
좋아요
어디로 갔어요?
Okay. Where did he go?
저한테 들은거 아니예요
멀홀랜드 드라이브 1919번지요
You didn't hear this from me.
1919 Mulholland Drive.
나올 수 있어요?
Can you get out?
아니요 못 가요
새라가 여기 와서
No. No. Not until
you get down here
여기 수갑 찬걸 풀어줘야돼요
and get the key to get me
out of these handcuffs.
잘됐네요
거기 있어요
Good. Then stay there.
네? 안돼요! 안돼!
잠깐만요! 새라! 안돼요 안돼!
What? No, no, no! Wait! Wait!
Wait! Wait, Sarah! No, no! Wait!
7년동안 맥가이버 본걸
드디어 써먹네
Those seven years of MacGyver
finally paid off.
넌 여으면 안돼
You shouldn't be here.
날 멈추려면 날 죽여야할거야
You want to stop me,
you're going to have to kill me.
난 네 파트너야
Well, I'm your partner,
절대 너 혼자
들어가게 하지 않겠어
and I'm not letting
you go in alone.
알겠어
Okay.
가자
Come on.
Um... computer emergency?
컴퓨터 고장나셨나요?
차 안에서 기다리고만 있었어요
I was waiting in the car.
진짜예요
I swear.
안녕 존
Hello, John.
그리고 친구분들
And friends.
유감스럽군
This is unfortunate.
당신이 어디로 도망치든, 숨든
No matter where you run, where you hide,
나도 항상 거기서
I'm going
to be there,
기다리고 있을거야
waiting.
조심해
Please be careful.
항상 자신감 차있고
Always so proud,
정의롭지, 존
so righteous, John.
하지만 내가 할 일이 있어서 말이야
But I have business to attend to.
자네가 방해하게
둘 수가 없군
I can't have you interfering.
신의를 중요시 하는
사람인줄 알았는데
I thought you
were a man of honor.
내가 당신 팀에 들어갈
실력이 안된다면
If I'm not good enough
to make your team,
총 없이도 날 이길 수 있겠지
surely you could defeat me without the gun.
예우있게 말이야
Withhonor.
자네 말이 맞군
You're right.
여러분
My students,
특별 수업이다
this is a special lesson:
어떻게 예우있게
사람을 죽이는지 보여주지
How to kill a man with honor.
It will happen
순식간에 이뤄질거야
very quickly.
케이시, 호랑이의 눈!
(영화 Rocky의 대사)
Eye of the tiger, buddy.
닥치고 있어, 척
Shut up, Chuck.
미안해요
Sorry.
우리 이제 큰일난거죠?
We're in trouble, aren't we?
뱀 기술을 써요
옭아매요!
Use the snake on him.
Get around him.
어서요!
Come on!
케이시 때려요!
Casey, hit him!
케이시가 밀려요
He's outmatched.
평정심을 잃었군, 존
You lost your calm, John.
집중을 전혀 안하고 있어
Your center
is filled with conflict.
그거야
That's it.
???
케이시 케이시 케이시
일어나봐요
Casey... Casey!
Casey, you gotta get up.
- 어서 일어나요
- 도망쳐, 척. 어서
- You gotta get up.
- Run for it, Chuck. Go.
정말 안됐군
It's too bad,
really.
내 사람들이 자네 실력이
I was hoping my
men would see
좀 더 나아진걸
봤으면 싶었는데 말이야
better skills
from a former student of mine.
이제 케이시가 어떤 기분인지 알겠어요
Look. Look, I get how you're
feeling, man. I totally
알겠다고요
정말 아끼는 사람한테
get how you're feeling.
You're feeling betrayed
배신을 당해서 배신감을 느끼는거예요
by someone that
you really care about.
도움이 전혀 안되잖아, 척
You're damaging my calm, Chuck.
평생 사람들을 밀어내고
You've spent so much of your life-
pushing people away.
고함치고 욕하고
때려대기만 했어요
Lashing out with purple words
and... and punches.
이제 왜 그랬는지 알겠어요
But I know why you do it.
겁이 나서 그랬던거예요
You do it because you're scared.
뭐?
What?
무서웠던거예요
사람들이 알게 될까봐
Scared. Scared to be known.
우리가 당신이 정말
어떤 사람인지 알게되면
Scared that, if we see
who you really are,
정말 케이시를
좋아할까봐 겁이 났던거예요
we'd actually care about you.
닥쳐!
You shut up!
네 조용히 해요 척
화만 돋우고 있잖아요
Yeah. Shut up, Chuck.
You're making him mad.
겉 모습은 무섭지만 그 안에는
Underneath that extremely
terrifying exterior lies a man
마음이 따뜻한 남자가 있는거예요
who deeply, deeply feels.
케이시는 우릴 좋아해요
You care. You care about us.
나 좋아하잖아요
인정해요
You care about me.
Admit it. You feel all
따뜻하고 인정이 많잖아요
warm and mushy about me.
어서요. 말해봐요
Go ahead. Say it.
당신은 날 사랑해요
존 케이시
You love me, John Casey.
죽여버릴거야!
I'm going to kill you!
잠깐 잠깐! 아뇨
나 말고요
Wait, wait, wait! Hold on.
No. Not me.
저 사람
Him.
수고했어요 스승님
Nice work, sensei.
네. 케이시한테는
평정심이란게 없단게 문제였어요
Yeah. Well,
the thing is, Casey doesn't
really have a calm center.
분노라면 또 모를까
It's more of an angry center.
잘 봐
There he is.
너네들 스승이야
There's your sensei.
어쩌고 있는지 잘 봐
Take a good
look at him.
이번엔 누가 덤빌래?
Who's next?
머리 위로 손 올려!
Hands on your heads!
네가 장군한테 전화했지
You called Beckman.
네? 제 잘못 아니예요
What? It's not my fault.
새라가 찍은거예요
She guessed.
자 이제 이 달의 우수사원을
발표하도록 하겠습니다
And now it's time
to announce this month's
Employee of the Month.
잘은 몰라도
다들 최선을 다하셨겠지요
And, for what
it's worth, you all tried your... best.
고객 서비스에서
최고점을 받은 직원은..
The employee with
the highest level
of customer service is...
스킵 존슨!
Skip Johnson!
내 잘못 아니야
멍청하게 군다고 굴었는데..
It's not my fault.
I tried to be a jerk.
축하해요!
Oh, congratulations!
물론, 바이모어 액자에 영원히 이름과
Clearly, there is no prize that I could
give you
사진을 남기는것 만큼의
만족스러운 선물은 없겠죠
that would compare to the satisfaction
of having
your name and photo immortalized
on a Buy More plaque.
내가 뭐랬어?
What did I tell ya?
이럴줄 알았지
So lame.
하지만 한번뿐인
특별상을 받아주세요
However,
please accept
this one-time only bonus gift.
65인치 평면 TV입니다
A 65-inch flat screen TV.
상이 구릴거라며?
??
오늘 날 구해줘서 정말 고마워, 척
Well, thanks for saving my life
today, Chuck.
언제든지요. 케이시
Anytime, Casey.
Yeah.
케이시는 내 친구잖아요
You know what?
You're my friend.
그래. 너도 내 친구야
Yeah. You know what?
You're my friend, too.
그것 참 고마운 얘기네요
케이시. 잘 자요
Well, that's really kind
of you, Casey.
Have a good night.
고마워
Thank you.
방금 뭐라고 했어요?
무슨 얘기 했잖아요
You said something, didn't you?
You said something.
뭐 말했잖아요
You said something!
들었어요
다 들었어요
I heard that. I heard that.
누나
Hey.
저녁 약속 못 지켜서 미안
Sorry I missed
tonight.
일 때문에 빠져나올수가 없었어
I got stuck at work.
괜찮아
새라가 얘기했어
It's okay.
Sarah told me.
근데 데븐네 부모님은 어디 계셔?
Uh... Where are
Awesome's parents?
데븐이 공항에
모셔다 드리고 있어
He's, um... he's taking
them to the airport.
오늘 못 온거
정말 미안해 누나
I really am sorry about
missing the dinner, Ell.
시부모님이 되실 분들하고
I mean, I know
it's important for you
만나는 중요한 자리였는데..
to let your future in-laws
meet your family and...
척, 있지. 난..
You know, I, um...
한번도 내 결혼식이 어떨지
꿈꿔본적이 없었어
I've never been
one of those girls
that dreamed about what
their wedding day would be like.
어떤 드레스를 입을지
What I would wear.
어떤 남자와 결혼을 할지도 말이야
Even the person
that I would marry.
그냥 다 막연한 생각뿐이었어
It was all kind
of, uh... kind of hazy.
하지만 한가진 확실했어
Except... except
one thing was clear-
아빠 손을 잡고 나갈거라는거
That Dad would walk me
down the aisle.
누나
Hey, Ellie.
그러지 못할거란거 잘 알아
I know it's not
going to happen.
근데 그걸 포기하기가
너무 힘들어
It's just... it's just really
hard to let go of that.
항상 너희들 생각을 한단다
생일 축하한다. 아빠가
ALWAYS THINKING OF YOU.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, DAD.
지금 거신 번호는 결번이오니..
The number you have reached
is not in service.
왜 그래?
What is it?
누난 아빠 손 잡고 결혼할거야
Dad's going to walk
you down the aisle.
그런 소리 하지마, 척
You can't say that, Chuck.
날 위해서 하는 말인건 알지만
I know that you
want that for me,
오랫동안 연락이 없으시잖아
but we haven't heard from him
in a really long time.
알아. 내가 찾아낼거야
Yeah. Well,
I'm going to find him.
나 똑똑하잖아
I'm a smart guy.
찾아낼 수 있어
I can do that.
누나가 결혼한단 소식 들으면
And, when he hears
about the wedding,
꼭 와주실거야
he'll be here for you.
척, 정말 아빠가
와 주실거라고 생각해?
Come on. You really
think he's going to make it?
내가 약속할게
I guarantee it.
네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)